原创翻译  双语字幕
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我们需要人类来保护人类
We need humans protecting humans.
当开国元勋们说
I mean, when the Founding Fathers said,
"人人生而平等"
"All men are created equal."
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
他们指的是人
They meant men.
他们并不是指来自太空的蟑螂
They didn't mean some roach from the vacuum of space.
你愿意做我的下一任外星事务部部长吗
How would you like to be my next Director of Alien Affairs?
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
我想推一条报道  是关于L公司的
I wanted to pitch you a story. It's about L-Corp.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
我的线人发现了不少的"黑预算"
My source caught rumors of a "Black budget."
我如果要战斗  就应该知道自己的能力
If I'm supposed to fight, I need to know what I'm capable of.
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
谁把木屑放进我的咖啡杯里的
Who put wood chips in my coffee cup?
我以为树人吃木屑呢
I thought that's what Dryads ate.
后期     你是不是饿得慌
曼彻斯特在用饵钓我
Manchester is baiting me.
我想做一个和平的人
I want to be a man of peace,
但我浑身上下都在反抗这一想法
but every fiber of my being is fighting against that.
总监     你是不是饿得慌
你在考虑重新拿起那把剑吗
Are you considering picking the sword back up again?
我的戒指去哪了
Where's my ring?
现在是精英的时代
This is the era of the Elite.
树上猫  银行劫匪  都交给你
Cat in a tree, bank robbers, all yours.
但是种族主义者  法西斯主义者  自由之子
But the racists, the fascists, the Children of Liberty...
我们来管
That's our department.
好精神  饱肚子  输不了
Clear eyes, full tums, can't lose.
只要这个仇恨者倒了
Just so long as after this hater goes down,
我们就重新做正事
we get back to the real task at hand.
这就是正事
This is the real task at hand.
正是小事
Real small task is right.
朋友们  我保证今天的事
Friends, I promise tonight's job
会和我们革命性任务有异曲同工之处
will very much be in the spirit of our revolutionary mission.
好了  现在来同步我们的手表
Right. Now, let's sync our watches,
这样我们就能在约定的地点时间见面了
so we can meet up you know where, you know when.
另一边见
See you on the other side.
或许可以先去吃点甜点
Maybe a little snack first.
梅纳热里
Menagerie.
你在打那位女士的主意吗
Were you going after that nice lady?
女孩总得吃饭
Girl's gotta eat.
-精英在哪里  -你问了我也不会说
- Where are the Elite? - Like I'd tell you.
告诉我们  不然就吃这个
Tell us or eat this.
梦想者  放松点
Hey, Dreamer. Easy.
我以为你是说
I thought that you said
当超级英雄就要展示力量
being a superhero was about showing strength.
我指的是"手叉腰"
Well, I meant more "Hands on hips,"
不是"当面吼"
not "Screaming in face."
明白了
Gotcha.
精英不可能一直逍遥法外
The Elite can't run forever.
告诉我们他们在哪  我们或许会从轻处理你
Tell us where they are, and we might go easy on you.
你胆敢碰我身上一片鳞片
If you touch one scale on my body,
我的朋友就会让你尝受到第五维度的痛苦
my friends might transport you to a Fifth Dimension of pain.
最后一次机会
Last chance.
曼彻斯特在哪里
Where is Manchester?
我非常谦逊地
It is with great humility
接受由总统任命的
that I accept this presidential appointment
外星事务部新部长一职
as your new Director of the Bureau of Alien Affairs.
本次任命将是新黎明到来的象征
This appointment will signal the dawning of a new day.
今天  人类将不再提心吊胆地活着
A day in which human beings need no longer live in fear
恐惧外星人及其随机袭击...
of aliens or their random acts of--
和我的小朋友问个好
Say cheers to my little friend.
外边怎么样了
How's it looking out there?
超女
Supergirl.
你救了我们的命
You saved our lives.
那里
There!
该走了  伙计
Time to go, mate.
-什么  但我差点就搞定他了  -这样就够了
- What? But I nearly got him. - Nearly will have to do.
超 女
第四季 第十四集
奥尔森先生
Hi, Mr. Olsen.
伊芙  感谢你能来
Hey, Eve. Thanks for coming in.
咖啡  两块糖  正是你喜欢的
Coffee, two sugars, just how you like.
你居然记得  谢谢  真贴心
You remembered. Thank you, that's very kind.
为了我最喜欢的前老板义不容辞
Hey, anything for my favorite ex-boss.
别告诉格兰特女士我这话
Don't tell Ms. Grant I said that.
我绝对不会的
I most certainly will.
那你见我想要做什么
So what did you want to see me about?
我只想问你几个问题  如果可以的话
Uh, I just wanted to ask you a few questions, if that's okay.
好吧
Sure.
请吧...
Please, um...
那么  几周前
So, uh, a few weeks ago,
我桌上有份报告
I had a report put on my desk,
详细描述了一笔L企业的
That detailed a black budget
黑资金
at L-Corp.
通常我会自己去深挖
Normally, I would be digging into this myself,
但我想鉴于你与那里的关系...
but I figured with the nature of your relationship there...
你觉得应该先来问问我吗
You figured you'd ask me first?
可能更简单些
It's probably easier.
当然  这类事情我要去和
Obviously, this is something I'm going to have to talk about
卢瑟女士谈谈
with Ms. Luthor.
但是没什么需要担心的
But there's nothing to worry about.
黑资金是被当做一种工具
The black budget is a tool we use
用来保护我们专利科技不受竞争对手侵害
to shield proprietary science from our competitors.
所以没什么黑幕吗
So nothing's off?
奥尔森先生
Mr. Olsen,
你和卢瑟女士现在关系很僵硬
you and Ms. Luthor are in a rough patch.
看看外面的情况
Look at it out there.
莉娜正在尽力改善那个现实
Lena's trying to help make that reality better.
人类与外星人紧张局势达到沸点
不过经过她同意后
Still, with her approval,
我可以把资金发给你  你可以自己看
I will email you the budget, so you can see for yourself.
但我保证  我们做的是好事
But I promise, we're one of the good guys.
-谢谢你  伊芙  -理所应当
- Thank you, Eve. - Of course.
卢瑟女士
Ms. Luthor.
我刚刚得知你拒绝在志愿者身上做试验
I was just informed that you're refusing to test my volunteers.
这是真的吗
Is this true?
是的
Yes.
血清的提纯等级仍在百分之九十以下
The serum's purification level is still below 90%.
现阶段  人体实验风险太大
At this point, human trials are too great a risk.
-我不同意  -这不由你决定
- I disagree. - Well, that's not your decision.
国内的紧张局势很严峻
Tensions in this nation are high.
为了维护和平
To keep the peace,
我需要我的士兵尽快变得最强
I need my soldiers to be as strong and as fast as they can be.
我需要超级士兵
I need them super.
这我理解
And I understand that,
但科学是催不出结果的
but rushing science is not the answer.
我们没有那么多时间
Time is a luxury we do not have.
你以为我不知道吗
Don't you think I know that?
我和你一样希望血清尽快完成
I want this serum as quickly as you do,
但我拒绝过早进行可能会害死特工的试验
but I refuse to rush anything that may kill your agents.
士兵们每天都冒性命危险
Soldiers take risks every day.
我只是需要更多时间
I just need more time.
好吧
Fine.
但记住  请你来是叫你完成任务的
But remember, you were hired to do a job.
尽快
Do it.
卢瑟女士  有件事我得告诉你
Ms. Luthor, I need to tell you something.
伊芙  晚点再说好吗
Eve, can we discuss this later?
这才是今天唯一重要的事
Today, this is the only thing that matters.
好吧
Okay.
我由东向西绕了地球两圈
I circled the Earth twice east to west.
我是由北向南  有发现吗
North to south for me. And?
到处都没有精英的踪迹
No sign of the Elite anywhere.
我早该在有机会的时候
I should have dealt with this Manchester business
解决曼彻斯特
when I had the chance.
你把他交给警方了  你还能怎么样
You brought him to the police. What more could you do?
精英跟洛克伍德和自由狂热分子一样糟
Now, the Elite is as bad as Lockwood and his Liberty fanatics.
现在唯一重要的是找到他们  结束这一切
Look, all that matters now is that we find them and we end this.
典型的超级英雄发言
A classic superhero speech.
但首先我们得处理一下梅纳热里
Just, first, we should really do something about Menagerie.
再听她教我怎么穿鞋我会疯
There's only so much footwear advice I can take.
白天古驰  晚上普拉达
Gucci all day and Prada all night.
你们不能这么做
You can't do this.
超女送给我们一份礼物
Supergirl left us a present.
还有留言
And a note.
上面说"不客气"
Says, "You're welcome."
她确实做到了在一天内制伏精英一员
Well, she did manage to take down one of the Elite
还阻止了对洛克伍德的刺杀
and stop Lockwood's assassination in a day.
那听起来你能喘口气了
Then it sounds like you've got some breathing room.
这是好事
Which is a good thing.
总统叫我给你分配一个安保任务
The president asked me to reassign you to a security detail.
安保  保护谁
Security? Whose?
保护我
Mine.
但请不要担心  丹弗斯局长
But please don't worry, Director Danvers.
我为和平而来
I, uh... I come in peace.
保护本·洛克伍德
Guard Ben Lockwood?
开玩笑吗
You can't be serious.
总统不开玩笑
The president doesn't joke.
洛克伍德是个凶手
Lockwood is a murderer.
看着他的人应该是狱警
The only ones that should be watching over him are prison guards.
局长  你宣誓过要保卫国家安全
Director, you swore to keep this country safe.
保护本·洛克伍德也包括在内
Protecting Ben Lockwood does just that.
激进分子想要刺杀他
Now, extremists are out to kill him.
假如他们成功了  就要闹革命了
And if they succeed, we will have a revolution on our hands.
还有其他可以胜任的特工
There are other qualified agents.
对付有敌意的外星人
No one has more experience
没有人比你更有经验
dealing with hostile extra-terrestrials than you.
总统也很清楚
And the president knows it.
假如你对自己的工作有不满
If you've got an issue doing your job,
你得上报给他
you need to take it up with him.
看起来你摆脱不了我了
Well, looks like you're stuck with me.
十点有新闻发布会  我们走吧
Press conference at 10:00. Shall we?
总要这么久吗
Does it usually take this long?
预知梦境吗
The dreaming?
她对梦境空间的掌控变快了
Her handling of the dreamscape is getting faster,
但精英可能在任何地方
but the Elite could be anywhere.
你跟她说过私下里不用穿战服吗
Have you told her she doesn't have to wear the suit in private?
过阵子就好了
It's just a phase.
我刚成为超女时也这样
I did the same thing when I became Supergirl.
连睡觉都穿着
I practically slept in my suit.
说句实话
And, I mean, let's face it.
战服很酷啊
The suits are pretty cool.
是啊
Yeah.
荣恩  精英似乎让你特别烦心
J'onn, the Elite really seem to be getting to you.
哪里不对劲吗
What's wrong?
曼彻斯特让我感受到了
Manchester brings out feelings in me
许久未曾有过的感觉
that I haven't felt in a very long time.
我不喜欢这种感觉
I don't like feeling like this.
失控的感觉
Like I could lose control.
我不知道这种情绪是哪里来的
And I just don't know where it's coming from.
我们都有受不了的人  荣恩  这很正常
We all have people that push our buttons, J'onn. It's natural.
好
Yeah.
曼彻斯特就是我的肉中刺
Manchester gets under my skin.
还好火星人的皮比较厚
Well, good thing Martians have thick skin.
我们已经派人去了你华盛顿和科林伍德的住宅
So, we have teams set up at your D.C. and Collinwood residences,
每小时都会有人跟我汇报
and I should be getting an update every hour.
我必须得说  能有人类来管理超查部
I have to say, it is so great to finally have a human
真是太好了
in charge of the DEO.
总觉得一个
I mean, the idea that an alien
致力于逮捕外星人的机构
would be running the very department
由外星人管理怪怪的
in charge of policing aliens.
你是从超查部特工那里听说的吗
Did you hear that from the DEO agent
就是被你变成恐怖分子的那位
that you turned into a terrorist?
不  是总统说的
Uh, no, from the president.
好吧
Okay.
我知道你觉得我是个怪物
I know that you think that I'm a monster.
但是在第二次世界大战之前  半数英国人
But half of England said the same thing about Winston Churchill
对温斯顿·丘吉尔的评价也是如此
before World War II.
我们只能走着瞧了
So, I guess we'll just wait and see.
历史会证明我是对的
History will prove me right.
洛克伍德部长  你打算怎么消除国内恐怖主义威胁
Director Lockwood, how are you going to stop domestic terrorism?
我很好  谢谢你的关心
Well, I'm great, thank you for asking.
我并不想聊精英组织
Listen, I don't really want to talk about the Elite
以及他们昨晚试图刺杀我的行为
or their assassination attempt on me last night.
我想与大家讨论的
Instead, I would like to discuss with you
是我之前没能声明的东西
what I was prevented from announcing.
我想要废除《外星人赦免法》
My drive to repeal the Alien Amnesty Act.
因为这么久以来
Because, for too long,
许多外星罪犯来到了这个星球
alien criminals have come down to this planet,
并且得到了赦免
and they have been given amnesty.
他们得到了保护
They've been given protection,
但我们才是需要保护的人
when we are the ones that need protecting.
我们才是经受折磨的人
We are the ones who have been suffering,
而不是他们
not them.
《外星人赦免法》废除后
With the repeal of the Alien Amnesty Act,
我们应该将这些入侵者
I propose that we send these invaders
赶回他们的星球
back to the planets that they came from,
这样我们才能最终平静地生活
allowing us to finally live in peace.
我希望邀请大家明天
I would like to invite you to a rally tomorrow
在这栋大楼的广场上集合
in the main concourse of this very building,
我将与大家分享我打算呈给国会的东西
where I will share with you what I intend to share with Congress.
他不能这样做
He can't do that.
告诉我  本·洛克伍德无权废除国会法案
Tell me Ben Lockwood cannot repeal a congressional act.
确实如此  但他可以发动人们一同请愿
No, but he can try and sway the will of the people.
他这是求着精英再杀他一次
Well, he's just begging the Elite to take another whack at him.
所以我们需要在集会前找到他们
Which is why we have to find them before his rally.
要是知道去哪里找就好了
If only we knew where to look.
阳台
The balcony.
外星事务部大楼对面
Across from the Alien Affairs building.
跟昨晚的地方一样吗
The same place as last night?
我在梦里见到了
I saw it in my dream.
回到犯罪现场
And returning to the scene of the crime
是典型的坏人行径
is a classic bad guy move.
-多克斯特工  -在  长官
- Agent Dox? - Yes, ma'am.
洛克伍德部长发表宣言之后
Since Director Lockwood's little announcement,
一支支持外星人的队伍被召集起来与其对峙
a pro-alien march has been organized to counter his rally.
这支队伍的核心力量
Someone going by "AmericanAlien"
美国外星人 纳欣诺市游行
自称是"美国外星人"
is at the center of this one.
我需要你黑进留言板
I need you to hack into the message board
看看有没有极端分子想要煽风点火
and see if any extremists will be showing up to stir the pot.
你想阻止示威游行吗
You want to stop the march?
不
No.
但洛克伍德在武装自己的基地
But with Lockwood amping up his base
精英也在武装自己
and the Elite amping up theirs,
整件事可能会演变为火力争端
this whole event could turn into a powder keg.
无论这位美国外星人是谁
Well, whoever this AmericanAlien is,
他们的网站都进行了高度加密
their website is superbly protected.
对方应该是高智能加密爱好者
He or she must be a highly intelligent cryptophile.
-可能要花些时间  -赶紧动手  多克斯
- This may take some time. - Just do it, Dox.
-该死  -梦想者说他们会来这里
- Damn it. - Dreamer said they'd be here.
梦是可以引申的
Dreams are interpretive.
也许是和他们有关的东西
Maybe something about them is here.
或者是某一部分
Part of them is.
莫拉人的爪子
A Morae's claw.
你可以借此从心理上追踪莫拉人  对吗
You can use that to track the Morae psychically, right?
是的
Yeah.
我的天啊
Bloomin' heck, man.
-天啊  -这可真是壮观
- Bloody hell. - Well, isn't this a sight?
是啊  一大面冰墙
Yeah, a giant wall of ice.
你的朋友捣蛋鬼说钥匙在哪里
Now, where did your pal Mxy say the key was?
他没说
He didn't.
什么
What?
"在门垫下"吗
"Under the doormat"?
原来如此
Right.
不  不是金  是矮人星石
No, not gold, it's dwarf star.
大概有五百吨重
Weighs around 500,000 kilos.
好了  这些小家伙们可以解决
There. These little bad boys will do the trick.
不客气
You're very welcome.
我们就不能找材料给小莫做手套吗
Now can we please get something for Mo's mitt?
当然可以
Of course we can.
我打赌这里肯定能找到想要的东西
Oh, I wager we can find whatever we want in here.
你发了短信给我  什么事这么重要
You texted me. What was so important?
我要杀了本·洛克伍德
I am going to kill Ben Lockwood.
这么急找我就是为了这事
That? That was the emergency?
情绪突发  没错  我恨他
Emotional emergency, yeah. I hate him.
你和很多人都恨他
Well, you and a lot of people.
但不是很多人
Not "A lot of people"
刚接到命令要保护他
have just been put in charge of his security.
我接到了
I was.
-什么  -没错
- What? - Yep.
是总统下的令
By order of the president.
我不知道该怎么做
I don't know what I should do.
尤其是我这个时候应该出去
Especially when I should be out there
追查曼彻斯特和精英的下落
tracking down Manchester and the Elite,
我很肯定他现在还是他们的目标
who I'm pretty sure are still targeting him.
我相信超女会找到他的
Well, I'm sure Supergirl will find him,
并且赶在集会之前
and before that rally,
所以你不必担心洛克伍德
so you don't have to worry about Lockwood.
但是我怎么能昧着良心
Yeah, but how can I, with a clear conscience,
保护一个给世界带来这么多痛苦的人
protect a man who is causing so much pain in the world?
你是个英雄  艾丽克斯
You're a hero, Alex.
英雄要做出艰难的抉择
Heroes make tough decisions.
这话没让我更好过
Well, that's not very helpful.
这是你的工作  对吧
I mean, it's your job, right?
-对  -保护人们的安全
- Right. - You keep people safe.
无论你喜欢与否
And like it or not,
在集会上保护洛克伍德
protecting Lockwood at that rally
会保护在场所有人的安全
will keep all of those people safe.
人类和外星人
Human and aliens.
我觉得这是个好建议  或许吧
I thought that was good advice. I don't know.
的确是好建议
Well, it is, it is.
哈雷就是这么说的
It's just exactly what Haley said.
-一起吃吧  -不行  我有稿要赶
- Join me. - I can't. I have a deadline.
好吧
Okay, fine.
但锅贴全都是我的
But I call the potstickers.
-什么  -所有的锅贴
- What? - All of them.
不行  你太凶残了
No! That's ridiculous.
我们的意思是
All we're saying is,
如果我们有人要坐穿牢底
if one of us is rotting in a cell,
优先考虑的应该是把她救回来
it ought to be a priority to get her back.
我的意思是
And all I'm saying is, we'll fetch Menagerie
我们只要有办法避开超女就去救梅纳热里
as soon as we find what lets us get around Supergirl,
好让我们解决小本
so we can snuff Benny boy.
这是她的老巢
This is the belly of the beast,
一定有能毁灭她的种子
bound to be the seeds of her destruction somewhere.
或者
Or,
我们就利用这个
we just use this.
打倒超女  除掉洛克伍德
Taking down Supergirl and killing Lockwood
没法赢得人心
don't win hearts and minds.
但是这个
But this,
能让我们激发所有的外星兄弟姐妹
this'll let us activate all our alien brothers and sisters.
用它的小兄弟我们甚至可以做更多
And we can do even more with its little brother.
不要
Meh.
"Meh"?
那革命怎么办
What about the revolution?
除掉洛克伍德不是革命
Killing Lockwood is the revolution.
他们干掉我们一员  我们就除掉他们一员
They take one of us, we take one of theirs.
你把小菲当家人来看对吧
You loved Fi like blood, right?
难道你不希望谋杀她的凶手落网吗
Don't you wanna see her murderer go down?
但这不是我们最初的目的
Yeah, but that isn't what we set out to do.
我们本该改变世界
We're supposed to be changing the world,
而不是为了报仇参与自杀行动
not acting suicidal to settle old scores.
在老家  人们发现你和小菲不是普通人时
Back home, when the gang found out you and Fi were otherworldly,
我不顾万险为你挺身而出
I stuck up for you, at great peril.
你不能也为我这么做吗
And you can't do the same for me?
那不一样  你知道的
That's different, and you know it.
不  哥们
Nah, mate.
现在不一样的只有你
The only one that's different now is you.
拜托  莫  我们已经失去这一个了
Come on, Mo, we've lost this one.
但愿你找到你想找的东西
Well, I hope you find what you're looking for.
然后去死吧
And choke on it.
我可以感觉到莫拉  但我却看不到她
I can feel the Morae, but I can't see her.
有什么东西阻挡着我
Something's blocking me.
我有办法
I have an idea.
我不太明白你的话  但帽子的事我听你的
I don't quite get what you're saying, but I hear you about Hat.
人多反而误事
Too many cooks spoil the broth.
这东西不错
That's keen.
我们得立刻去找超女
We need to get Supergirl now.
我有预感我们要找的东西
Something tells me the thing we're looking for
就在这个拐角附近
is right around this corner.
曼彻斯特  结束了
Manchester! It's over!
不投降就受死
Yield or die.
狠话不用这么狠
Just take it down to, like, a seven.
不投降就算了
Yield or else.
新招数啊
That's new.
玩具不错
Fun toys she's got here.
到此结束了
This ends right now.
你说得对
You got that right.
曼彻斯特  不要
Manchester, no!
看它那张嘴  真是的
The mouth on that one, honestly.
美国外星人或是他们的网站有什么动静吗
Any movement on our AmericanAlien or their website?
没有
None.
他们数字指纹的最好情况是完整的
Their online fingerprint is generic at best.
最差情况是无法识别
Unidentifiable at worst.
不知道密码的话
Without knowing their key,
想获取留言板几乎不可能
accessing the message board is next to impossible.
游行队伍有多少人
And the march's head count?
一千多人
Hovering just over 1,000.
我们得让特工行动起来
We need to get agents on the ground for it.
是吗
Do we?
说到和平抗议
In thinking of peaceful protests,
我们应该想想妇女大游行
might we consider the success of the Women's March,
百万人大游行和自由游行的成功
the Million Man March, the Freedom March?
还有流血的天安门事件
Tiananmen Square,
1932年的酬恤金进军
the Bonus March of 1932.
有多少成功的故事
For every success story,
就有多少流血的故事
there's one of lives lost.
这次游行有近一千个外星人和外星人同盟
This march is filled with nearly 1,000 aliens or alien allies,
他们应受我们的保护
which fall under our protection.
出了差错就是我们的责任
And if anything goes wrong, it's on us.
组一支队伍
Organize a team.
很好
Very well.
我去把特工美国外星人的信息告诉赖夫特工
I shall update Agent Reiff on AmericanAlien's profile.
来不及了  我要你来领队
There's no time for that. I want you to lead it.
-我吗  -对
- Me? - Yes.
丹弗斯在洛克伍德的集会那里有支队伍
Danvers has a team at Lockwood's rally.
你们可以展开合作
You two should coordinate.
不敢相信
Still can't believe it.
谢谢
Thank you.
他就直接冲进屋里去了
He just ran straight into the room.
-停都停不下来  -那里面是什么
- He wouldn't stop. - What was in there?
一个小噬日者
A baby sun-eater.
是卡尔的
Kal's.
它会吞噬小恒星的化学质量
It feeds on the chemical mass of small stars,
就像个定时炸弹
so it's basically a living bomb.
荣恩
J'onn...
很奇怪  我一直都能感应到曼彻斯特
It's strange. I've always been able to sense Manchester,
感受到他的狂暴  他的愤怒
feel his rage, his anger,
但现在感应不到了
but I can't anymore.
感觉就像重担减轻了
It's almost like a weight has been lifted.
-我甚至觉得有点  -释然
- I almost feel-- - Relieved?
有时候  只有别人离开了我们才知道
Sometimes we don't realize the impact people have had on us
他们对我们的影响有多大
until they're gone,
无论这种影响是好是坏
for good or bad.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你们两个
Both of you.
或许他现在终于获得宁静了
Maybe now he can find some peace.
可现在帽子在外作怪  我们就有任务在身
Still, the Hat's out there, and we have a job to do.
我虽然没有图腾
I may not have a totem,
还是能试着从精神上分析他在哪里
but I can still try searching for him psychically.
那我们呢
What about us?
我们监控新闻  注意是否有情况
We monitor the news and see if anything pops up.
我想找特伦特·米勒
I was hoping to speak to Trent Miller.
他是法务会计师
He's a forensic accountant.
他在帮我处理一项预算
He's looking into a budget for me.
是吗  那...
Oh, is that right? Uh, well...
等他回来  你能不能
When he gets back, can you
外星人在洛克伍德集会上游行抗议
让他给我这个号码打个电话
just have him give me a call on this line?
我是詹姆斯·奥尔森
It's James Olsen.
-谢谢  -妈  游行不会有危险的
- Thank you. - Mom, the march will be safe.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
再见
Bye.
去报道游行很紧张吗
Nervous about covering the march?
还好
I'm fine.
紧张也没关系  弗兰克林
No, it's okay if you are, Franklin.
这就是个疯狂的时代  对吧
I mean, we are living in crazy times, right?
重要的是要记住我们的职责
It's just important to remember what we do here every day.
报道这样的事件
Reporting on events like this,
冒着危险展现事件的不同面
taking the risk to show all sides,
让大家看见人性
and showing the humanity there,
这不亚于做一名英雄
that's nothing less than heroic.
你这么想
I mean, think about it.
你用拳头对抗不公
You fight injustice with your fists,
或许能帮助一个或十几个人
you can help one, maybe a dozen people.
但出色的新闻报道
But good journalism,
可以影响数百万人
that can impact millions.
这就是我们成为记者的初心  对吗
It's why we became journalists in the first place, right?
对
Yeah.
-谢谢  奥尔森先生  -不客气
- Thanks, Mr. Olsen. - No problem.
-弗兰克林  -怎么了
- Franklin. - Yeah?
你需要摄影师吗
You need a photographer?
成千上万的外星人与其支持者
Thousands of aliens and their supporters
涌上街头...
have turned out in the streets of--
-布莱尼  -大家好啊
- Brainy. - Greetings.
你怎么穿着战服
Why are you in your suit?
提前习惯一下
Breaking it in.
我什么都没感应到
I have nothing.
帽子肯定躲在五维空间了
Hat must be hiding in the Fifth Dimension.
那里的能量让他无法被追踪到
The energy there makes him untraceable.
我听说曼彻斯特死了
Yes, I heard about Manchester's passing.
那他拿走的军团戒指  我的那枚
Um, the Legion ring he took, my ring,
是不是...
was it...
好吧
Oh, well.
这件事算是解决了
That's put to bed now.
对了  今天是游行的日子对吧
Ah, yes. It's the march today, isn't it?
你们都要参加吗
Will you all be joining?
你知道吗  我们今天都需要来点和平的抗议
You know, I think we could all use some peaceful protest today.
-好的  我会去的  -很好
- Yeah, I'll be there. - Wonderful.
卡拉  尼娅  梦想者
Kara? Nia? Uh, Dreamer?
是的  我确实认为我们应该去...
Yes, I definitely think we should be there.
-太好了  -去巡逻
- Huzzah! - To patrol.
-什么  -梦想者和超女想法一致
- What? - Dreamer stands with Supergirl.
我先热热身
Just gotta stretch first.
好的
Oh, right.
卡拉  我能和你说句话吗
Um, Kara, uh, a word?
我觉得今天如果超女一起游行会更有意义
I think it would mean a lot to have Supergirl march today.
我也希望自己能去  布莱尼
I wish I could, Brainy,
但是我认为我更应该去巡逻
but I think it's more important for me to patrol
以防有事发生
in case anything gets outs of hand.
不会有事发生的
They won't.
我就是美国外星人
I am AmericanAlien.
标签  美国外星人
Hashtag AmericanAlien.
是你组织的抗议
You... You organized it?
我丢失军团戒指时
When I lost my Legion ring,
我意识到我太依赖于它来获得力量
I realized how much I depended on it for strength
和自信
and confidence.
我以为它让我成为了英雄
I thought it's what made me a hero.
但是过去几天没有戒指的日子里
But not having it these past few days
让我意识到并不是戒指给了我力量
has made me see it wasn't my ring that gave me strength.
而是与你们并肩奋战
It was fighting alongside all of you,
帮助地球成为更好的地方
helping to make the Earth a better place.
在这样的时代  变革不会因为
In times like this, change won't come
拥有戒指或是披风的人而发生
from someone with a ring or a cape.
只有当我们每个人都响应号召
It'll only come when each one of us
弘扬信念  变革才会到来
answers the call to stand up and be heard.
聚则强
El Mayara. Stronger together.
我们是超级英雄
Just because we're superheroes
并不意味着我们忘记了自己是谁
doesn't mean we forget who we are.
对不起  布莱尼
I'm sorry, Brainy.
风险太大了
The risk is too great.
准备好了
Ready.
超女也许是一个象征
Supergirl may be a symbol,
但更重要的是  她是地球的一份子
but, more importantly, she's a citizen of Earth,
就像我们一样
like the rest of us.
记住这点
Remember that.
我们今天为了团结一致而聚集在此
We are gathered here today to unite.
作为人类美国人团结起来
To unite as human Americans
夺回我们的土地  这一切始于
to take back our great land, and that all starts
废除《外星人赦免法》
with the repeal of the Alien Amnesty Act.
外星人不是敌人
团结一致
多克斯特工  报告情况
Agent Dox, sitrep?
我让小队进行边界检查
I have the team running perimeter checks.
我在绝佳的位置随时准备出动
And I am in a prime location to run interference.
蟑螂理应被杀死
Roaches get crushed.
蟑螂理应被捏碎
Roaches get squashed!
在游行队伍的南端有一些起哄的人
We've got some hecklers on the south end, alongside the march.
在路上了
On route.
回家吧  外星人
Go home, aliens!
妈妈叫你们回家了
Your planet called!
回家吧  我们这里不欢迎你们
Go home! We don't want you!
超女
Supergirl.
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我们来这里支持废除《外星人赦免法》
We're here to show our support for the repeal of Alien Amnesty.
但是赦免法给予了这些外星人权利
But that amnesty is what gives these aliens their rights.
他们为什么要得到任何权利
Why should they get any rights?
他们不过是来伤害我们的
They're just here to hurt us.
他们不是
They're not...
看看他们
Look at them.
他们不是来伤害任何人的
They're not here to hurt anyone.
绝大多数人都在逃离战争和暴力
Most of them are fleeing war and violence,
就像我当初刚来地球时一样
just like I did when I first came to Earth.
他们和你不一样
They're not like you.
你是超级英雄
You're a superhero.
不  你错了
No, you're wrong.
我和他们一样
I am just like them.
你们知道这些
Were you aware that these
外星人今天在此游行
aliens intend to march on this rally today
为了让我们住嘴
to quiet us, to silence you?
他们有权利这么做吗
Do they have the right to do that?
-没有  -好的
- No! - Okay.
我认为他们没有权利这么做
I didn't think they had a right to do that.
但是  我们都在学习  我们在学习
But, hey, we're all learning. We're learning.
我们在慢慢地学习
We're slow, but we're learning.
我们在向他们学习  我们了解到
We're learning from them. We're learning
非我们即他们
that it is us or them.
Us or them.
非我们即他们
Us or them!
非我们即他们  非我们即他们
Us or them! Us or them!
超女
Supergirl.
我是卡拉·佐·艾尔  地球公民
It's Kara Zor-El, citizen of Earth.
很高兴你能和我们在一起
Nice to have you with us.
我也是
Me, too.
谢谢你们
Thank you
你们两个人
both.
非我们即他们  非我们即他们
Us or them! Us or them!
赦免法和同情不同
Amnesty is not the same thing as empathy.
允许这些外星人来到我们的世界
Allowing these aliens to come to our world
不是一种善意的行为
is not an act of kindness,
而是一种全物种的自我破坏行为
it is an act of species-wide self-sabotage.
如果我们不废除《外星人赦免法》
If we do not repeal the Alien Amnesty Act,
他们不会毁灭我们
they will not be our undoing.
我们会毁灭我们自己
We will have done that to ourselves!
瞧  他们来了  非我们即他们
You see? Right there. Us or them!
非我们即他们  非我们即他们
Us or them! Us or them!
非我们即他们
Us or them!
他们要干什么
What are they doing?
他们要来从你们手里夺走你们的星球
They have come to take your planet from you.
今天...  今天我们说不
Well, today... Today, we say no!
今天  我们要把星球从他们手里夺回来
Today, we take our planet back from them!
不要动武
Stay peaceful.
不要堕落到他的水平
Don't stoop to his level.
非我们即他们
Us or them!
-我们现在得让你下台  -威胁在哪里
- We need to get you off the stage now. - Where's the threat?
你就是威胁
You are the threat.
好了  把他带出去
All right. Get him out of here.
把他带到安全的地方  远离这里
Take him someplace safe, away from here.
好喜欢临近中午的革命的味道
Mmm, love the smell of revolution in the late morning.
让我庆幸自己还活着
Makes me glad to be alive.
-谢谢你回来找我  -别客气
- Thanks for coming back for me. - Of course.
我们真的让他们误以为
We really tricked them into
你走进了那个噬日者的房间
thinking you walked into that sun-eater room.
而且当初我需要帮助的时候  你也伸出了援手
Plus, you were there for me in my time of need back home.
我能做的至少是回报你的好意
Least I could do is return the favor.
很高兴你开始接受我思考的方式
Just glad you've come around to my way of thinking.
走吧
Shall we?
非我们即他们  非我们即他们
Us or them! Us or them!
非我们即他们
Us or them!
这个世界上的外星人  这些蠢猪想杀了你们
Aliens of this world, these pigs want to kill you.
然后呢
And what?
你们打算坐以待毙吗
You're gonna take it lying down?
不
Oh, no.
我们该起义  把他们送进屠宰场
I say it's time we rise up and take them to the slaughter.
找到最近的外星仇恨者  然后杀了他们
So find the nearest alien-hater, and kill them!
革命现在开始了
The revolution is now.
把你们的超能力夺回来
Take your power back.
快上吧
Come on!
帽子一定是在孤独堡垒里救了曼彻斯特
Hat must have saved Manchester in the Fortress
然后藏在了五维空间
and then hid in the Fifth Dimension.
所以我感觉不到他
That's why I couldn't sense him.
全息图
Hologram.
-那真的曼彻斯特呢  -在附近
- Then where's the real Manchester? - Close.
鉴于信号的强度
Given the strength of the signal,
发送半径肯定小于一个城市街区
the broadcasting radius must be less than a city block.
好的  布莱尼  尼娅  你们清理现场
Okay. Brainy, Nia, you clear the area.
-我来对付...  -把曼彻斯特留给我
- I'll handle-- - Leave Manchester to me.
好的  就像我说的
Right, like I said.
荣恩去抓曼彻斯特  我来找帽子
J'onn's got Manchester. I'll find Hat.
是时候换装了
Time for a costume change.
厉害  太厉害了
Brilliant. Bloody brilliant.
总是慢一步  荣恩
Always one step behind, J'onn.
你能看见我
You can see me.
曼彻斯特
Manchester!
你一个
One for you.
And one for you.
你一个
你好  帽子  我们又见面了
Hello, Hat. We meet again.
这不是丢了戒指的那位吗
Well, if it isn't the Ringless Wonder.
有朋友的时候你并不需要戒指
You don't need a ring when you have friends.
那你的朋友现在在哪呢
So where are your friends now?
干得好  布莱尼
Nice work, Brainy.
现在把他带去超查部
Now get him to the DEO,
然后尽你最大的努力
and then help me get as
把更多的人带到安全的地方
many of these people to safety as you can.
回你的星球去  蟑螂
Go back to your planet, roach.
不要  求你了
No, please!
滚出去
Get out of here.
-谢谢...  -梦想者
- Thanks, uh... - Dreamer.
很高兴城里又多了一位超级英雄
Nice to have another superhero in town.
你是要告诉我  菲奥纳不想看到我变成这样
Is this where you tell me Fiona wouldn't want to see me this way,
而且我的灵魂还值得拯救吗
and that my soul's still worth saving?
不是
No.
我觉得菲奥纳死了  你很高兴
I think you're glad Fiona's gone.
什么
What?
没有她挡道  你就有理由做这些事了
With her out of the way, it gives you an excuse to do all this!
这是为了正义
This is for justice!
你也有同样的理由
You have the same excuse, too!
你的妻子  你的女儿们
Your wife, your daughters.
或许你只需要失去更多
Maybe you just need to lose more.
再来
More!
我们现在把彼此了解得更清楚了  荣恩
I think we're seeing each other much clearer now, J'onn.
谢谢你  超女
Thank you, Supergirl.
不  谢谢你
No, thank you.
如果不是因为曼彻斯特
I think if it hadn't been for Manchester,
这次游行本该很成功
the march would have been a success.
即使不成功  通过这种抗争
Even if it wasn't, amidst all the fighting,
我能感觉到人们团结在了一起
I could feel people coming together.
-我们改变了一些人的想法  -和人心
- We changed some minds. - And some hearts, too.
即使在哥谭市和大都会的抗议中
I mean, even in the protests in Gotham and Metropolis,
没人受伤  人们尊重彼此的差异
no one got hurt, people respected each other's differences.
甚至是昨天
Even yesterday,
我看到了人性真正的流露
I saw some real moments of humanity.
正如你照片中记录的一样  奥尔森先生
Like in your photo, Mr. Olsen.
一张照片就能改变舆论  这总是令我感到惊讶
It always amazes me how one image can change the conversation.
没错  今天早上我在电梯里听到
Exactly. I heard, in the elevator this morning,
有人说你的照片感动了他们
someone say that your photo moved them so much
他们要去外星人服务中心做志愿者
that they're going to volunteer at an alien outreach center.
很高兴能为此献一份力
It feels good to be a part of the progress,
但真正的功劳归于超女和她的新伙伴
but the real credit goes to Supergirl and her new sidekick.
如果可以  我很想做她们的独家新闻
I'd love to get an exclusive with them if I could.
伙伴
Sidekick?
我马上就去联系
I'll get right on that.
-谢了  -奥尔森先生
- Thanks. - Mr. Olsen?
你得看看这个
You need to see this.
当然
Sure thing.
-"她的新伙伴"  -我不知道
- "Her new sidekick"? - I don't know.
-是我吗  -我没告诉他
- Me? - I didn't tell him.
由于昨天的示威
Oh, and as a result of yesterday's demonstration,
总统和我
the president and I, um,
认为在采取任何进一步措施前
think it's best to hold congressional hearings...
最好就此事举行国会听证会  感谢大家
on the matter before we take any further steps. Thank you very much.
我们成功了
We did it.
我们阻止了法案的废除
We stopped the repeal.
至少暂时是
For now, at least.
媒体的力量真是惊人
The power of the press is an amazing thing.
人们的力量也是如此
So is the power of the people.
丹弗斯局长
Director Danvers.
很高兴看到你回归超查部
It's good to see you back in the DEO.
很高兴能回来  上校
It's good to be back, Colonel.
洛克伍德这位官僚根本不了解自己的权力
Lockwood is a bureaucrat with power he doesn't understand.
这不仅让事情更加危险
Not only does that make things dangerous,
-也让我们难以开展工作  -是的
- it makes our job difficult. - Yeah.
不过你昨天表现得很好
But you were a good solider yesterday.
把你的职责置于政治生命之上
Putting your duty above your politics.
没有多少人能做到这一点
Not many would have been able to do that.
谢谢你
Thank you.
混乱中诞生了积极的力量
From all that mess comes something positive.
看来美国外星人是个好人
Looks like AmericanAlien was one of the good guys after all.
-她让人  -捉摸不透
- She's very... - Confounding.
-是的  -是的
- Yes. - Yes.
你的前任很会拍照
Your ex is pretty good with a camera.
我读了小报
I read the tabloids.
一场内战正在酝酿之中
There is a civil war brewing.
我都能闻到它的气息
I can smell it in the air.
但这个国家或许还有希望
But there might be hope for the country yet.
时机似乎暂时对你有利
Seems time is on your side for now,
所以今晚休息一下
so take the night off.
看来明天又是新的一天了
Well, I guess tomorrow's another day.
明天或许就太迟了
Tomorrow may be too late.
你在哪里  曼彻斯特
Where are you, Manchester?
或许你只是需要失去更多
Maybe you just need to lose more.
你无法改变我
You can't change me.
今天我要以火星猎人的身份找到你
Today, I find you like a Manhunter.
等等  你得重新讲
Okay, wait, wait, wait. You have to go back to the part
你痛打了本·洛克伍德的那段
where you strong-armed Ben Lockwood.
-我的天  你太爱血腥了  -求你了
- Oh, my gosh. You so have a bloodlust. - Please.
我不知道  这件事太疯狂了
Oh, I mean, I don't know, the whole thing was crazy.
我以前从来没有经历过这种事
You know, I've never been through something like that before.
我知道超女和我
And I know that Supergirl and I
最近意见都不一致
haven't really been on the same page lately,
但是  看见她在游行队伍里
but, you know, seeing her out there at that march
与其他人手拉手
hand-in-hand with everybody else,
我受到了鼓舞
I was inspired.
嗯  然后痛打了本·洛克伍德
Yeah. To rough Ben Lockwood up.
不  不
No, no.
不  那个...  我
No, it was, you know, I...
我遵循了自己的信念  而不是规矩
I followed my beliefs, not the rules.
站在道德的立场上感觉棒极了
And it felt really good to take a moral stance.
是的  我想在游行中的所有人都感觉到了
Yeah, I think everyone at that march felt that way.
看到所有这些人站出来表达他们的信念
Seeing all those people come out to have their convictions heard.
-还有詹姆斯的照片  -对
- And James's photos. - Yeah.
看见人们尽力互相帮助  那真的...
Seeing people who'd been fighting helping each other, that was...
这就表明
It just goes to show,
不管你是谁  外星人  人类  超级英雄
no matter who you are, alien, human, superhero,
每份行动都有价值
every action counts
每个声音都很重要
and every voice matters.
谁知道  也许好人最终会胜利
And who knows, maybe the good guys will win in the end.
没错
Exactly.
干杯
Cheers.